Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there?
Hold on for me!
On this long journey that
we've only barely begun!
Friendship, love, courage,
and a little bit of fun!
These are the things.
That even as the years go by!
Will not ever vanish from our minds!
We are all pieces of
a single planet Earth!
Little by little we can
find each other's worth!
And as we see what sort of
form we're meant to take!
All of us know the wind will
always keep on blowing away!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look through that wind to dry!
All the tears as you're bleeding!
The things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
All the tears you shed will help
you to become so much stronger!
All the tears you shed
will help you to remember!
Everything, everything, everything!
Now and forever!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, yay!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you
as you finish what you've begun!
Let's do that wind to dry all the tears as
you're plating the
things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure,
found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there!
Hold on for me!
Oh, crap!
I gotta get out of here!
It's truly quite hot down here.
Warden! Wait, please!
Give us a second!
Don't start fighting it!
Everyone, clear out!
The warts' poison will get us, too!
You suck!
I was finally gonna make it to all
that awesome-smelling food over there!
Jawboy, whatever you do, don't fight him!
Listen, that's Magellan,
the warden of Impel Down!
He has the power of the venom venom fruit!
He's the last person
you ever want to fight.
Make a run for it!
Venom Venom version? He's poison?
Indeed I am.
You're a bit out of your
elements, Straw Hat.
Even though you're a rookie,
I expected more from a pirate
with a bounty of 300 million.
Especially one who has caused the
world government so much trouble.
Speaking of trouble,
I can't imagine how you managed to worm
your way through security, but here you are.
Rest assured, you will suffer
for tarnishing my reputation.
I know why you're here, by the way!
You came to rescue your brother,
Portgas D .A.,
2nd Division Commander of the Whitebeard
Pirates You've had quite
the little rampage,
but all of that will come to an end now.
And one final thing, I will find out
exactly how you broke into my prison!
You will spill every
last juicy detail to me.
I just wish, I wish I could
do more to help you, but!
I'll die before I say a word.
Listen, please!
Magellan's whole body is poisonous.
Crazy, terrible poison.
If you so much as touch
him, you're finished!
You can't bait a guy like that. I will.
Let's go back the way we came.
To the pool of blood.
This way, give up on that stupid food.
And let's hightail it to level 5.
There's no escape!
The staircase to level 5 is protected by
three demon guards and their commander.
Every exit on this floor has
already been accounted for.
There will be no more running.
This is your?
No!
I won't believe it!
I can't believe it!
Hydra!
What the heck is that?
A venom monster?
Thing is poison?
Warden Magellan, wait, please.
We're still evacuating.
The warden guy's poisoning his own people.
The hydrous venom is a
paralytic neuron, Johnson.
It makes its way through your body.
Causing horrific pain
before you finally die.
It's killing me.
Give me the antidote.
Hurry! Boss, why?
Stay out of the way when I'm
fighting, you damn fools.
You got that?
We're terribly sorry, sir.
Stop chasing me.
I just want to eat.
How do you think about
food in a time like this?
Either way, you've got to respect
a man that knows what he wants.
I admire your bravery, dear friend.
It just sucks that
we're both going to die.
Touch me if you can, Hydra!
Ah, I forgot it's really hot!
Oh, right!
One of the heads is gone!
How clever.
You have some of your
brother's cunning after all.
Chloroform ball!
That was close!
Put your gas masks on!
Stay clear.
The warden's in the middle of a battle.
What is this? Sear gas?
No, it's Magellan's poison.
Go somewhere else to fight, you bastards.
Who's he up against anyway?
I don't know.
Maybe that intruder
they were talking about.
So hell heat plus poison gas?
Give me a break.
My eyes, it's like crazy.
What's happening to me?
I can't fight!
Fight like this?
Whoa, the Hydra!
Stop moving!
Down the Venom road.
Try as you might.
Oh!
One touch and it's over.
He's melting through the stone.
First the wall, and then you.
I've gotta rescue Ace!
Surely, even you must know
that your death is imminent.
Just like Ace.
I'm telling you, we have to make a move
while Magellan is busy with Straw Hat!
Are you out of your mind?
Look how many gods there
are down there. It's nuts.
That doesn't matter.
Just think about it.
They assign the more powerful demon guards
to protect the staircase to level five.
It's more important to them to not let
Straw Hat get down to the lower levels.
Meaning they are the crappiest
security they have here.
If we miss this chance, soon
after they'll time their defenses.
Straw Hat will lose at some point.
Once he does, this window is closed.
We must get to level
three before that happens.
Actually, maybe you're right.
I've never heard anything about Vice Warden
Hannibal having any Devil Fruit powers.
If I can take out those guards
with a muggy ball, we can do it.
Hannibal can't be that tough
right now. You're thinking?
All right, let's do it.
I don't want to stay in.
this heat one moment longer.
It's now or never.
Ready?
Nothing is going to stop
us from getting through.
That's right.
Vice Warden Hannibal.
Look, it's Buggy the Clown and Mr.
Three.
Looks like they're trying
to get to level three.
We can't let those bastards go any higher.
Let's go.
Now, McGee! Can do! Wait a minute!
Guards, stand down.
No, come, come!
Oh, damn!
Warden Magellan guards the
most dangerous criminals
in the most infamous
prison in the entire world.
He's the lord and master of hell itself.
You're not going to let Strawboy
face him alone, are you?
Oh, forgive me.
There's just no way to meet him.
I tried to warn you,
but you wouldn't listen.
Running is the only answer.
I'm sorry, Strawboy. I'm a coward.
Forgive me.
I suggest you put an end to
this nonsense and submit.
I'm going to rescue my brother, and
we'll escape from here together.
I won't die without even seeing him.
And I'm not going to let you
execute him, you hear me?
What's that smoke?
I don't have time for your tricks.
I'm not getting anywhere.
I can't win without touching you.
I'll make a sacrifice.
You can take my arms, but I won't lose
Why would I need your arms?
You want me to take you
apart piece by piece?
Oh, gong gong!
Jet bazooka!
Morons, what's wrong with you two?
If you had just slipped
away when I told you to,
I could have blamed
this mess on the warden.
We're at the staircase to level three.
There was a raid by two of the escapees.
We've got some casualties here.
Yes, that's right.
We have Buggy the Clown and Mr.
Three in custody.
You wanted to go through the gate.
I said fine, but you wouldn't believe me.
Ruin my plan.
Ow.
He's a hell of a lot
stronger than he looks.
Damn Hannibal.
I don't want to be tortured if
that's what's in store for me.
I'm going to bite off my tongue.
I'm serious.
Here I go.
I'm going to do it.
I'm really going to do it.
There's no way we can beat Magellan.
I'm not gonna dream an impossible dream.
If I'd remain there any longer, I'm
200 % sure he would have killed me.
Don't look back.
Just keep running.
The only thing I can do is run.
It would seem you have
brought me to my knees, boy.
Even a cornered rabbit will
fight with teeth and claws.
But now, your hands and arms
are covered in my poison.
You're feeling the pain.
I know you are.
Now come go!
Twins it for kill!
Venom!
Glowfish!
See you like this!
Gum-Gum! Hydra!
Ten pistol!
Fuck!
Vision getting blurry?
Are your ears ringing?
Your hands have become
useless, haven't they?
In time, my poison will
take everything from you.
Hey, Jailor.
Want to do a condemned man a favor?
Tell me, is something
happening on the upper levels?
No, not a thing.
No, come, come!
Stop!
Are you finally done?
No!
Second gear!
Hydra!
My wife!
My brother!
Consider this your punishment, child.
There's no way to neutralize the amount
of poison your body has absorbed.
You will suffer an agonizing pain
for 24 hours, and then you will die.
This is true hell.
Warden Magellan!
Excellent battle, sir.
What should we do with Luffy?
Any orders?
He'll die soon, but we don't
want him just lying there.
Throw him into the central tower
of Level 5 until further notice.
Yes, sir!
Warden Magellan!
Bad news, sir!
There's a problem over at
the staircase to Level 3!
That's the area Hanyable
and his men were guarding.
What's happening there?
I don't know the details, sir!
Hey. Hey!
Guess he's gone.
He's either stone-cold dead
or hibernating for the winter.
Sounds nice.
Damn, my fingers are shot.
I can't move them.
I can't even feel them.
Sounds like frostbite.
Sorry, you're history.
I can't even bite my stinking bread.
Can we stop by the burning hell for a sec?
Check it out.
They're dragging in a newbie.
Sucks to be him.
Hey, pal, what's your name?
How much is your bounty worth?
Come on, talk to us!
Looks like he's nearly dead.
Magellan's already given
him a taste of his poison.
I leave for a moment, and
this is what I return to?
Ennubo, I counted on
you, and you let me down!
Wake up, you imbecile!
What the hell happened here?
Warn it, please!
You're choking me!
I was caught off guard.
I'm sorry, sir.
No!
Don't torture us!
Torture stinks like ass!
And by the way, mine is very
sensitive, so please don't whip it!
Some nutty martial artist
ballerina did all this.
I'll be frank with you.
He took us by surprise, sir. Silence.
No excuses.
You let him slip away and he escaped
to the upper levels, didn't he?
It seems that prisoner used to be
part of Crocodile's baroque works.
He's the one who used to call himself Mr.
Two.
He's rather odd.
I don't care.
At any rate, I wouldn't worry, sir.
I feel confident that
we'll catch him in time.
And what of the riot on level two?
Any updates it's winding down
almost under control sir.
I want all the guards on level four
to proceed to level three immediately
I also want all of mistress 80's
demon guard searching for the escapee.
I'll leave the rest to you right and
what about these two sir do as you like.
Just make sure this mess is all cleaned up
and things are in order
by the time I get back.
I'm going to head over to
my private place for a bit.
My tummy oh the runs hey
move it get off your asses
we still have one last
escapee we need to track down.
Yes right away sir um excuse me vice warden
what do you want to do with these two.
Oh I want to ask them
a few questions get an
interrogation room I'll
take charge of them.
Personally right understood
sir I'll make the preparations.
okay then they're all yours right
too
easy.
yes no one's whipping my buttocks
tonight okay that's that now what do we
do don't play dumb you know what's next
we need to hurry up and rescue straw
hat before it's too late you're still
hung up on that didn't you hear them
saying that he's been poisoned by
magellan and taken to level five it's too
late to save him there's no way he'll
survive and will be caught tortured
and die like dogs it's a bad plan why
should we risk our lives to save someone
who's as good as dead that won't stop
me I'll gladly die like a dog for
him after turning my back on straw boy
I'm already dead inside the least I
do is make things right.
I thought that it was better to run and
save myself than to suffer the same fate,
but I swore that if there was
any chance he would survive,
I'd return,
put my life on the line, and rescue him.
And I meant it.
So, I must come to his aid.
Yeah, that's a real touching
story, but now you've escaped.
You're almost a free man.
Why would you want to go back out there,
guns a-blazin' and risk your life again?
Because I'm his friend I don't
need any other reason that's it
First we gotta deal with that poison
there's surely they have some sort of
antidote but then Where would it be you
think there's still time to get an antidote
nah I wouldn't bother shut up Already
both of you this is something this is
something I have to do don't die on me
straw boy Hold on a little bit longer.
No freaking way.
I mean, uh, what do you mean
you can't make an antidote?
What is the holdup?
No one ever survives after Warden Magellan
douses them with that much
of his special attack.
If it was just one kind of poison, maybe.
But his is a special multifaceted toxin.
There are just too many
variables to account for.
I'm afraid it's impossible, Vice Warden.
What the? You're kidding!
And your people call
yourselves a medical team?
Lies! Huh?
I mean, the answer lies
ahead. Just keep trying.
We have to turn Straw Hat Luffy over to
the Navy, and I want him alive for that.
But even if we think we're on to a cure,
if we administer any sort
of medication incorrectly,
he'll most likely die even sooner.
I told you, it's hopeless.
Let it go and move on.
You heard them.
There is no antidote.
You'd be throwing your
life away for nothing.
Now, let go of that nonsense
and think about escaping.
Let's find a way out of here together.
No one survives a battle with him.
It would take a miracle.
A miracle?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
I forgot about him.
He's in Impel Down.
My hero.
The Miracle Worker.
When doctors give up on a
patient, he can still save them.
He can even save a dying country.
His list of miracles is legendary.
He's the greatest the
queen of all queens Eva
Come on.
We need to find out where
they're holding him now.
We need to
What?
Sir level five yep,
that's where we're
headed prisoner transfer
these two were sentenced
to freeze to death
Keep walking, scumbags.
I realize this is a bit of a long
shot, but I have to do anything I can.
This list of prisoners is presenting more
questions than it's answering, I'm afraid.
Like this, for example.
Empire Ivankov, the real name of
Eva, has been crossed off in red ink.
Has he been released already, or
has he been secretly executed?
Tell me something.
Did we let this prisoner go free? What?
Oh, you mean Ivankov?
Love, you know what happened
to him a few years ago.
You know what?
Wait, Vice Warden, you forgot?
Huh?
Oh yeah, of course, I remember.
Now let's see if you know, huh?
But there are prisoners present, sir.
I don't care, out with it.
Every so often, people
disappear in Impel Town.
We're sure they didn't just break out,
as some of the missing could barely move.
They just vanished without a trace and
no one seems to know the cause we've
come to call it demon in the way all the
guards here have come to fear these are
natural and strange disappearances we
believe that those missing have been dragged
to the gates of hell hence why we call it
what we do so people just up and vanish?
Creepy i wish i'd never
heard that yes same here
The door's not even open
and it's already freezing!
And we're even wearing heavy
clothes this is it as a fair
warning the army wolves are
quite hungry today now i'll
take them from this point on
just as usual huh you'll take
what well your weapons and
coats sir huh honestly sir we
don't know how you do it you
always tell us i'll show every
single prisoner the courage
of the vice warden and then
march forward into the freezing
hell without a weapon or
even a coat sincerely we're big
admirers of you for it no way
also because they're
inappropriate for prisoners
to have we'll be taking
their coats as well now.
Hand them over.
Our coats, too!
Say what?
Right. Take care now.
And don't forget, transponder snails
won't work, thanks to the cold and all.
Safe travels.
Why?
I can barely use my hand. It's so cold.
Feels like the wind.
Watching me in the face.
Hold on.
I've almost got it.
It's unlocked!
Yes, you did it. Thank you.
There you are.
One, two, three, four.
Hey, don't tell me these aren't
army wolves, are they? But why?
Shouldn't they be on the floor
of the wild beasts from hell?
What do you mean?
Oh, I think I know why they're not.
It's because they would eat the other
beasts like the basilisk in the sphinx.
It's for their protection.
No way!
These mangy little fleabags
are really that dangerous?
You gonna deal with
these damn things, too?
The cold was bad enough.
Now I've got another reason
for my teeth to chatter.
Why? Wanna fight? Make it quick.
Because I've got a
straw boy I need to say.
Screw this!
I'm not going to be their dinner!
What?
You're running already?
Come on, this is messed up.
Do we really have to sit here
and just watch this kid die?
I have to save him.
He's the only brother I've got.
You'll be nothing more than a
leaf whipped about by a storm.
An insect flicked away by hands
far mightier than your own.
Stop fighting it already.
Listen, you can't survive
after taking that much poison.
I'm sure you can't see.
But can you at least hear me?
Just accept your death graciously.
I won't! No!
Look!
I'm not gonna die till I rescue Ace!
How do you expect to save somebody
when you can't even save yourself?
Who is it anyway?
Some friend of yours? How stupid.
In prison, it's every
man for himself, got it?
No one's coming to help you.
That's just the way things are.
We're all alone down here.
In the sea of fire, you'd trample all
over someone else in order to stay alive.
When you face the beast,
you'd kick another prisoner
straight into their hungry jaws.
You'll die if you care
about anyone but yourself.
So cut all the
I-wanna-rescue-someone crap.
Understand that talk makes me sick
Look somebody's coming.
I don't recognize him.
He's not one of the jailers
Wait a minute is he making?
Stop I I've come here to rescue you!
In the name of our everlasting friendship!
Who the hell is that?
He's covered in blood.
Before I I ran away
Hey pal how do you know him
He's my friend straw boy
I'm not letting you die
He left the keys?
I never thought about breaking
out of here until now.
I gotta find Eva before it's too late.
Eva, huh?
I have no idea where
that Twinkle Toes went.
Who the hell wants to know anyway?
Empire Ivankov.
Oh, that guy. Yeah.
He's probably dead.
Who are you staring at?
That guy's been missing for ages.
What do you even want with him?
And how did you get out of your cell?
Get me out of mine, too!
Do you know why they're
keeping a man named Eva?
Hey, you! What's wrong? Hey! Speak up!
Answer me! Don't bother. Didn't you notice?
Everyone in that cell is frozen stiff.
How about you, then?
Yeah, I heard you.
Said you're looking for Ivankov, right?
Yeah.
Do you know something?
Look, over there.
You see that forest? Yes.
There's an abandoned jailhouse,
way beyond the tree line.
A while back, I saw this strange
guy just dancing around out there.
Really?
Yeah, I think it was him.
It's worth a look.
Thanks, friend.
We're all in this together.
That forest, it's where
the wolves live. Oh, is it?
We believe that those missing have
been dragged to the gate of hell.
Hence why we call it what we do.
The gates of hell, demon-ing away.
Quit pulling my tail.
No way Eva disappeared because of
some superstitious mumbo-jumbo.
I've never met him myself, but his
reputation certainly precedes him.
Even in a hell like this place, I'm
sure he can still make a miracle happen.
Because Eva is our queen, our god!
Somehow I know he can save straw boy if
we can't count on an antidote anymore.
He's his only chance.
Eva I swear I'll find you no matter what.
Oh, my God.
Straw boy!
What do you think you're
doing to my friend Bon?
Leave him?
Oh, straw boy, how did you?
The public execution of Five Fist
Ace will take place in 26 hours.